<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Crystal Drop</title>
    <description>Crystal Drop is the endless arcade faller you’ll never want to put down.
</description>
    <link>http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 22:13:56 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 22:13:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.2</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>User Research Personas</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;samuel-casual&quot;&gt;Samuel (Casual)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;primary-motivation-for-playing-mobile-games&quot;&gt;Primary Motivation for playing mobile games:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I play mobile games to pass the time while waiting or when I’m bored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Associated motivations: 
I am a gamer at heart and generally enjoy games of different types.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;key-significant-differences&quot;&gt;Key Significant Differences&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Considers himself a casual mobile gamer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Does not enjoy mobile gaming as a primary source of entertainment.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mixed feelings toward tilt controls.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;personal-information&quot;&gt;Personal Information&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;age&quot;&gt;Age:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;22 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gender&quot;&gt;Gender:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Male&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;major&quot;&gt;Major:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Computer Science&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ethnicity&quot;&gt;Ethnicity:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;African-American&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;phone-type&quot;&gt;Phone type:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Android&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;technical-informationmobile-game-use&quot;&gt;Technical Information/Mobile Game Use&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;mobile-game-use&quot;&gt;Mobile Game use:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Once a week&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;single-game-user-or-cycle-through&quot;&gt;Single game user or cycle through?:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cycle through&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;length-of-use&quot;&gt;Length of use:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;30 minutes to an hour&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;experienced-with-touch-based-games&quot;&gt;Experienced with touch based games:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;likes-high-score-games&quot;&gt;Likes high score games:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;competitive-gamer&quot;&gt;Competitive gamer:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;likes-freerunnerendless-faller-games&quot;&gt;Likes Freerunner/Endless Faller games:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sometimes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feelings-and-concerns&quot;&gt;Feelings and concerns:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Feels that competition can end friendships&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Has mixed feelings toward tilt controls; feels they can be unreliable&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is concerned that high score systems can sometimes be gimmicky or out of place&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;personal-profile&quot;&gt;Personal Profile&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“We don’t have a good example of a tilt based game. Cool, but needs to be capitalized.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Samuel, mobile games are just a way to pass the time. He generally cycles through multiple games looking for something that interests him enough to lose track of waiting, and is generally neutral towards freerunners or endless fallers; he’s open to trying them, but is indifferent at first glance. 
His general level of interest in mobile games is moderate. He would rather be playing a more serious game or doing something more interesting, but if the occasion calls for it he will play them. He is willing to make exceptions if the mobile game is especially entertaining however, and will then commit much more time to playing it. 
Samuel views some games as “gimmicky” due to their forced inclusion of a high score system or tilt control, but feels that under the right circumstances such things could end up being beneficial.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;samuels-goals-for-a-mobile-game&quot;&gt;Samuel’s Goals for a mobile game&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would like to see a fun, accurate tilt-based control system.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would like avenues for friendly competition, as long as it doesn’t cause anger.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would like a game that engages his interest more than most.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;primary-persona-represents-61-of-respondents-who-play-mobile-games-1&quot;&gt;Primary persona: represents 61% of respondents who play mobile games. [1]&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;chloe-mid-core&quot;&gt;Chloe (Mid-Core)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;primary-motivation-for-playing-mobile-games-1&quot;&gt;Primary Motivation for playing mobile games:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I play mobile games for fun and personal achievement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Associated motivations: 
I like interactive games that are well made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;key-significant-differences-1&quot;&gt;Key Significant Differences&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Considers herself a mid-core gamer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enjoys mobile gaming as a hobby.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Least likely to play competitively.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;personal-information-1&quot;&gt;Personal Information&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;age-1&quot;&gt;Age:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;23 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gender-1&quot;&gt;Gender:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Female&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;major-1&quot;&gt;Major:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Game Design&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ethnicity-1&quot;&gt;Ethnicity:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caucasian&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;phone-type-1&quot;&gt;Phone type:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Android&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;technical-informationmobile-game-use-1&quot;&gt;Technical Information/Mobile Game Use&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;mobile-game-use-1&quot;&gt;Mobile Game use:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Four to five times a week&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;single-game-user-or-cycle-through-1&quot;&gt;Single game user or cycle through?:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cycle through&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;length-of-use-1&quot;&gt;Length of use:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;30 minutes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;experienced-with-touch-based-games-1&quot;&gt;Experienced with touch based games:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;likes-high-score-games-1&quot;&gt;Likes high score games:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;competitive-gamer-1&quot;&gt;Competitive gamer:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;likes-freerunnerendless-faller-games-1&quot;&gt;Likes Freerunner/Endless Faller games:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;feelings-and-concerns-1&quot;&gt;Feelings and concerns:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dislikes competition; Plays more for achievement.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is indifferent to tilt controls; feels they need to be well done to be worthwhile.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Gets upset when she loses and doesn’t want that to affect friendships.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;personal-profile-1&quot;&gt;Personal Profile&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“I tend to get easily upset when I lose, so to keep my friendships, I try not to play against my friends.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Chloe, competition is something she wants to avoid. While she sometimes likes to measure her own progress by high scores or achievements, she doesn’t want to compare herself to friends or strangers. For her, it just brings too many bad emotions to the surface that she doesn’t enjoy. 
However, she is quite interested in mobile games and likes to try a wide variety based on what catches her eye. It needs to be fun and well made, while offering a bit of a challenge. She also enjoys endless runners and faller styled games, having tried multiple titles in the genre, but they’re not her primary focus. 
She tends to play in short bursts of 30 minutes, but she plays frequently throughout the week to check in on her progress or beat that high score she set last time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;chloes-goals-for-a-mobile-game&quot;&gt;Chloe’s Goals for a mobile game&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would like an achievement based game.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would like avenues for friendly competition, as long as it doesn’t cause anger.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would like a game free of Player vs Player elements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;secondary-persona-represents-28-of-respondents-who-play-mobile-games-2&quot;&gt;Secondary persona: represents 28% of respondents who play mobile games. [2]&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;nathan-hard-core&quot;&gt;Nathan (Hard-Core)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;primary-motivation-for-playing-mobile-games-2&quot;&gt;Primary Motivation for playing mobile games:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m looking for my new gaming addiction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Associated motivations: 
I like games that either have a good story or fun mechanics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;key-significant-differences-2&quot;&gt;Key Significant Differences&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Considers himself a hard-core gamer.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Enjoys mobile gaming as a hobby.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dislikes some competitive elements; hates seeing how bad he is.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;personal-information-2&quot;&gt;Personal Information&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;age-2&quot;&gt;Age:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;22 years&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;gender-2&quot;&gt;Gender:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Male&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;major-2&quot;&gt;Major:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Mechanical Engineering&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ethnicity-2&quot;&gt;Ethnicity:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Caucasian&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;phone-type-2&quot;&gt;Phone type:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;iPhone&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;technical-informationmobile-game-use-2&quot;&gt;Technical Information/Mobile Game Use&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;mobile-game-use-2&quot;&gt;Mobile Game use:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Multiple times a day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;single-game-user-or-cycle-through-2&quot;&gt;Single game user or cycle through?:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cycle through&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;length-of-use-2&quot;&gt;Length of use:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;15-30 minutes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;experienced-with-touch-based-games-2&quot;&gt;Experienced with touch based games:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;likes-high-score-games-2&quot;&gt;Likes high score games:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Neutral&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;competitive-gamer-2&quot;&gt;Competitive gamer:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;No&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;likes-freerunnerendless-faller-games-2&quot;&gt;Likes Freerunner/Endless Faller games:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Yes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;feelings-and-concerns-2&quot;&gt;Feelings and concerns:&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dislikes boring games; needs to be engaged constantly.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Likes comparing scores, but doesn’t want the fun to be spoiled by competition.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Feels there needs to be good game mechanics to be viable as a long term mobile game.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;personal-profile-2&quot;&gt;Personal Profile&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“I do like comparing scores with friends, but being competitive is no fun for me.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For Nathan, mobile games are another potential source of an addiction that will keep his ever changing interests sated. He plays for the entertainment and achievement, liking to compare his scores to his friends but hating to see that his score stacks poorly compared to the best people playing the game. 
However, Nathan needs games that are interesting and engaging in order to devote time to them; if they’re just the same thing as every other game, then he will lose interest fast and move on. He also requires that the game have either good mechanics or a good story to keep him coming back for more. 
Overall, Nathan is moderately curious of mobile games as his interest is not exclusive to them, but easily can become so given the right game. Make it new, make it fresh, and make it exciting– this is what Nathan wants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;nathans-goals-for-a-mobile-game&quot;&gt;Nathan’s Goals for a mobile game&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Wants a game that offers a new, innovative experience.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would like a high score system, but wants to avoid seeing how he stacks up to strangers.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would like new game mechanics that aren’t copies of older games and don’t interfere with gameplay.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;tertiary-persona-represents-11-of-respondents-who-play-mobile-games-3&quot;&gt;Tertiary persona: represents 11% of respondents who play mobile games. [3]&lt;/h3&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/deliverable/2016/03/07/User-Research-Personas.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/deliverable/2016/03/07/User-Research-Personas.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Deliverable</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>User Research Summary</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;stakeholders&quot;&gt;Stakeholders&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our stakeholders consist of gamers around the ages of 20 to 30 that have a moderate to high interest in mobile games.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;user-research&quot;&gt;User Research&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During our research we used two methods of information gathering: structured and semi-structured interviews. We used structured interviews (online surveys) to gather information from our fellow classmates. This supplied us with very concise information. This also allowed us to compile the information efficiently so we could form conclusions in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We then moved on to semi-structured interviews to explore the more complex information such as prior games of the same genre and their likes and dislikes about them. We asked students around campus this time in order to increase our sample size to minimize potential bias. Changing to semi-structured interviews gave us access to new information we otherwise wouldn’t have been able to obtain due to the limited scope of responses that structured surveys provide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;research-findings&quot;&gt;Research Findings&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our research yielded some interesting information. To lay the groundwork, we asked their age, gender, ethnicity, and whether or not they were mobile gamer. Results showed that most responders were male with ages between 21 and 26. The ethnicities on the other hand were very balanced with a strong mix of Caucasian, Asian/Pacific Islander, African American, and Hispanic/Latino. Also, a vast majority said they are mobile gamers. We then asked some general questions their overall interest in mobile games, how often they play, and how long they typically play. The responses showed a very clear lean towards the more casual market. Most responders were either casual or mid core gamers with a moderate interest in mobile gaming. They often played simply when they were bored or had nothing to do at the moment (such as waiting in lines). Gaming sessions longer than an hour were scarce. Following questions showed that most responders were already familiar with the control features such as tilt and showed interest in having these features incorporated in games. Other features such high scores were a little less decisive. However, results still show a very strong support for having a high score incorporated into the game as well as competing with their friends’ scores. Finally, we asked if they had a previous experience with games of the same genre (endless fallers/runners) and whether or not they liked it and showed interest in playing more games like them. Once again, there was strong support for this genre of game with most responses claiming they would be willing to try more games like them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;design-requirements&quot;&gt;Design Requirements&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Supports Android and iOS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Game continues until the player dies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Incorporates touch and tilt controls
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Must feel natural&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Incorporates a High Score system&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Various enemies and zones&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;refined-design-question&quot;&gt;Refined Design Question&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How can we incorporate touch and tilt controls to create an engaging, interactive experience for users to enjoy with their friends?
* Explanation: Due to users showing such a strong emphasis on the controls feeling natural, we chose to focus as much as possible on keeping the controls to the game as natural and engaging as possible while also zeroing in on the casual competitive aspect of the high score system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;additional-information&quot;&gt;Additional Information&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Structured interview questions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Are you a mobile gamer?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is your gender?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is your ethnicity?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What mobile operating system do you use?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What level of gamer would you classify yourself? (casual, mid-core, hardcore)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is your level of interest in mobile games?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How long do you normally play mobile games?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How many mobile games do you prefer to concentrate on at a time?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do you have experience with touch-based games?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do you have experience with the tilting feature on mobile games?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How do you feel about games associated with high scores?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;How do you feel about competitive gameplay with friends?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do you play free-faller/endless runner games?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;If you answered yes to the previous question, how much do you like them?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Semi-Structured interview questions:&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Are you a mobile gamer? If yes, proceed with this interview.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Personal Information&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is your age?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is your gender?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is your ethnicity?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What is your declared major?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Are you an android user, iPhone user, or Windows phone user?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Requirement questions&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Would you consider yourself a casual, mid-core, or hardcore mobile gamer?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;definitions&quot;&gt;Definitions&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We classify casual as someone who only play games occasionally. Somewhere between a couple times a week to a couple times a month. This also could mean you stick to one type of genre of games.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mid-core would be someone who play closer to four to five times a week and play different genres of mobile games. They put time into the games they like and they have a couple of favorites.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Hardcore is considered someone who plays games multiple times a day. They are frequent players who tend to concentrate on either one genre they love in particular or diversify themselves into all their genres just as frequently. They tend to compete with friends or be competitive with anyone who also plays the same games as them.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;What is your level of interest in mobile games? (On a scale to 1 to 5)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;How long is a normal mobile game session for you? (In Minutes/Hours)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Do you normally play one mobile game at a time or cycle through multiple games? (Clarification: Are you only playing one game and concentrating on that single game, or do you tend to play multiple mobile games? Name of games not required.)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Are you experienced with touch-based games?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If no, what games do you have experience with?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Have you played games with a tilt feature?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If yes, do you like this mechanic?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If no, would you consider playing a game with a tilt feature?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do you like games that have a high scoring system?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If no, why not? (OPEN #1).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Do you enjoy playing competitively against friends?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If no, why do you not enjoy competitive game play?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Are you a fan of freefaller/endless runner style games?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If yes, which have you played?&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If no, would you consider playing one?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/deliverable/2016/03/07/User-Research-Summary.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/deliverable/2016/03/07/User-Research-Summary.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Deliverable</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mobile Game Survey!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Take our Mobile Game Survey Here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;!-- Change the width and height values to suit you best --&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;typeform-widget&quot; data-url=&quot;https://dhruvaldarji.typeform.com/to/VInnpn&quot; data-text=&quot;Mobile Game Survey&quot; style=&quot;width:100%;height:500px;&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;script&gt;(function(){var qs,js,q,s,d=document,gi=d.getElementById,ce=d.createElement,gt=d.getElementsByTagName,id=&#39;typef_orm&#39;,b=&#39;https://s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/share.typeform.com/&#39;;if(!gi.call(d,id)){js=ce.call(d,&#39;script&#39;);js.id=id;js.src=b+&#39;widget.js&#39;;q=gt.call(d,&#39;script&#39;)[0];q.parentNode.insertBefore(js,q)}})()&lt;/script&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2016 00:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/survey/2016/03/01/Mobile-Game-Survey.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/survey/2016/03/01/Mobile-Game-Survey.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Survey</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crystal Drop Origins!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Reject10 HQ where we are developing Crystal Drop!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Crystal Drop is our high score oriented free faller. 
Drop your way to glory as you guide the Crystal Sentry through treacherous tunnels, primeval jungles, and troubled skies.
As the game progresses, so will the difficulty, so make sure to evade all obstacles. 
Use touch and tilt controls on your mobile device to enable the Crystal Sentry, collect coins, 
and get a high score in both survival time and coins collected!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To track the progress of this game check out our &lt;a href=&quot;https://waffle.io/dhruvaldarji/CrystalDrop&quot;&gt;Waffle Board&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To track the development of this game check out our &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/dhruvaldarji/crystaldrop&quot;&gt;Github&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For any questions, comments, or concerns reach out to &lt;a href=&quot;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#116;&amp;#111;:&amp;#100;&amp;#104;&amp;#114;&amp;#117;&amp;#118;&amp;#097;&amp;#108;&amp;#100;&amp;#097;&amp;#114;&amp;#106;&amp;#105;&amp;#064;&amp;#103;&amp;#109;&amp;#097;&amp;#105;&amp;#108;&amp;#046;&amp;#099;&amp;#111;&amp;#109;&amp;#063;&amp;#115;&amp;#117;&amp;#098;&amp;#106;&amp;#101;&amp;#099;&amp;#116;&amp;#061;&amp;#067;&amp;#114;&amp;#121;&amp;#115;&amp;#116;&amp;#097;&amp;#108;&amp;#032;&amp;#068;&amp;#114;&amp;#111;&amp;#112;&quot;&gt;Dhruval Darji&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2016 00:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/origins/2016/02/12/Crystal-Drop-Origins.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://crystaldrop.dhruvaldarji.com/origins/2016/02/12/Crystal-Drop-Origins.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>Origins</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
